Guide to the Margaret Flory Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., Series XI
  - Missions: Board of Foreign Missions/Commission on Ecumenical Mission and Relations (COEMAR)/Program Agency Missions Unit
    - Board of Foreign Missions/COEMAR General Files: Events, Groups, Records, Miscellaneous
      - Staff Seminar -- Notes and Handouts, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 631)
      - Reformed and Presbyterian Jubilee, 1958-1960 (Box 70, Folder 632)
      - Community of Mission Consultation, Stony Point, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 633)
      - Advisory Study Committee (Ecumenical Relations), 1960 (Box 70, Folder 633a)
      - Commission Procedures, 1960-1963 (Box 70, Folder 634)
      - Personnel Practices, 1961-1964 (Box 70, Folder 635)
      - Laymen Overseas, 1961-1963 (Box 70, Folder 636)
      - Commission Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 637-638)
      - Organization Report, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 639)
      - Division of Relations, 1963-1964 (Box 70, Folder 640-641)
      - Missionaries/Fraternal Workers, Openings, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 642)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on University World Emphasis, 1965-1968 (Box 70, Folder 643)
      - Fall Planning Conference, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 644)
      - "The First Seven Years" Report, J.I. McCord, Chair, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 645)
      - Extension of the Church's Ministry in the World Consultation, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 646)
      - Staff Council, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 646a)
      - "Directions for the Sixties", 1966 (Box 71, Folder 647)
      - Administrative Council, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 648-649)
      - Division of Relations, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 650)
      - Staff Studies with Ruben Alves, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 651)
      - East Asia Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 652)
      - Ecumenical Affairs Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 653)
      - Europe Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 654)
      - Latin America Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 655)
      - Middle East Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 656)
      - Personnel Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 657)
      - USA Working Party, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 658)
      - Experimental Ministries in Mission, 1966-1968 (Box 71, Folder 659)
      - Fall Conference, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 660)
      - Staff Conference, Jan. 1967 (Box 72, Folder 661)
      - Fall Conference, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 662)
      - Office of Leadership Development, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 663)
      - Office for Planning and Research, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 664)
      - Renewal and Extension of the Church's Ministry in the World -- Coordinating Committee, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 665)
      - Reinforcement List, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 666)
      - Miscellaneous Internal Memos/Letters, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 666a)
      - Committee of the Whole, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 667)
      - Program Planning Group I: Christians Committed for Mission, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 668)
      - Program Planning Group II: Human Resources, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 669)
      - Program Planning Group III: Fruitful Witness to the Good News, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 670)
      - Program Planning Group IV: Meeting Human Needs with Integrity, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 671)
      - Program Planning Group V: Productive Partnership, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 672)
      - Program Planning Group VI: Open Style of Unity, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 673)
      - Program Planning Group VII: Reconciliation of Peoples and Nations, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 674)
      - Program Planning Group VIII: New Dimensions in Mission, 1967-1969 (Box 72, Folder 675)
      - Meeting Schedules, 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 676)
      - Missionaries in the U.S. List, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 677)
      - A Report From the World: Background Papers, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 678)
      - Crisis in the Nation Program (cf. "Race Relations" Subj. Files), 1968 (Box 73, Folder 679)
      - Staff Council, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 680)
      - Overseas Personnel in the Ministry to College and University Students, Directories, 1963-1964; 1968-1969 (Box 73, Folder 680a)
      - Directories, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 681)
      - Leadership Development Office, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 681a)
      - Investment Guidelines, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 681b)
    - People in Mission Unit
      - General
        - New Dimensions in Mission (M. Flory, Special Assignment), 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 682)
        - New Dimensions in Mission, Evaluation, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 683)
        - Center for Labor Studies Research Project (Wendell Jeanpierre, Lynne Edwards), sponsored by New Dimensions in Mission, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 683a)
        - Mission Program Services Unit: A Rationale, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 684)
        - Mission Program Services Job Descriptions, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 685)
        - Human Resources Planning, 1973-1977 (Box 73, Folder 686)
        - Volunteers in Mission: Asian Americans, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 686a)
        - Task Force on Patterns of Service: Report, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 687)
        - Mission Program Council, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 688)
        - Mission Funding Proposal: Bi-National Service, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 689)
        - Mission Funding Proposal: Ecumenical Sharing, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 690)
        - Mission Funding Proposal: Frontier Internships, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 691)
        - Mission Funding Proposal: Internationalization, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 692)
        - Mission Funding Proposal: Overseas Associates, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 693)
        - Overseas Associates, General, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 694)
        - Overseas Associates, Task Force Report, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 695)
        - Overseas Associates, Listings, 1976-1980 (Box 73, Folder 696)
        - "Affirm the Good News: Reaching People who are Without the Gospel", 1977 (Box 74, Folder 697)
        - Three-Way Mission, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 698)
        - Conferences on Overseas Mission, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 699)
        - Information Packet, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 700)
        - Patterns of Ecumenical Sharing, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 700a)
        - Staff Action Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 700b)
        - Mutuality in Mission, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 701)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1972-1980 (Box 74, Folder 702)
        - General -- Internal Memos and Letters, 1976-1980 (Box 74, Folder 703)
        - Lehmann, Paul; Brazil Project, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 704)
        - Minter, William and Ruth; FRELIMO, 1973-1976 (Box 74, Folder 705)
        - Manson, Joyce; Liaison for Europe, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 706)
        - Leaman, Harold, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 707)
        - Follow-up to Singapore Visit, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 707a)
        - re: Reinaldo Roa, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 708)
        - M. Flory Final Memos on Patterns of Ecumenical Sharing, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 709)
        - Directories, 1979-1981 (Box 74, Folder 710-712)
    - Education for Mission, Involvement in Mission, 1977-1983
      - General, 1977-1983 (Box 74, Folder 713)
      - General, Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 714)
      - Correspondence/Memoranda, 1977-1983 (Box 75, Folder 715)
      - Committees, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 716)
      - Open Doors Report, 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 717)
      - Papers/Articles, 1978-1980 (Box 75, Folder 718)
      - Conferences, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 719)
      - Global Profile Project, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 720)
      - Regional Mission Education Programs, 1978-1980 (Box 75, Folder 720a)
      - Pilot Project Report (2 copies), 1980 (Box 75, Folder 721)
      - Pilot Project Report, Abridged (2 copies), 1980 (Box 75, Folder 722)
      - Models and Designs Manual, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 723)
      - Information Packet, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 724)
      - Middle East Mission Update Study Packet, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 725)
      - International Christian Leaders Directory, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 726)
      - Dialogue and Interaction: Report, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 727)
      - Dialogue and Interaction Consultation: Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 728)
      - Global Education - History and Visioning, 1997 (Box 75, Folder 728a)
      - Futuring Global Mission Consultation, Louisville, KY, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 1307a)
    - Stony Point Center, NY
      - "Christmas at Stony Point," by M. Flory, in Outreach Dec. 1951 (Box 76, Folder 728a)
      - Gilmor-Sloane Center, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 729)
      - Conference on Mission in Global Perspective, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 730)
      - Reflections on the Sixth Assembly of the WCC, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 731)
      - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 732)
      - Global Village Event, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 733)
      - Centering (Journal), 1989-1993 (Box 76, Folder 734)
      - Annual Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 735)
      - Student Ministry Consultation -- rough notes and transcripts of working group discussions, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 735a)
      - Dear House, Mission Becomes You: Gilmor Sloane House, Stony Point Center, Stony Point, New York 1949-1999 by M. Flory, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 1245)
      - Centering (Journal), 1980, 1985-1999 (Box 123, Folder 1308)
      - "Centering Our Lives in Christ" by M. Flory, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1309)
      - Correspondence, 1989-2000 (Box 123, Folder 1310)
      - Fund-raising Information, 1987, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 1311)
      - Gilmor-Sloane Center, 1984-1988 (Box 123, Folder 1312)
      - Global Village, 1980, 1988 (Box 123, Folder 1313)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1314)
      - News clippings and letters of congratulations to M. Flory about the publication of Dear House, Mission Becomes You: Gilmor Sloane House, Stony Point Center, Stony Point, New York 1949-1999, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 1314a)
      - Stony Point Programming Committee and Events, 1981-1988 (Box 123, Folder 1315)
    - 150 Years of Presbyterian Witness (1837-1987)
      - General
        - Committee for the Celebration of 150 Years of Participation in Ecumenical Mission (Box 76, Folder 736)
        - Thurber/Magruder Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 737)
        - Leadership Development Program (Box 76, Folder 738)
        - Presbyterian Women and Mission (Box 76, Folder 739)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 740)
      - Resources
        - Magazine Coverage (Box 76, Folder 741)
        - Bibliographies (Box 76, Folder 742)
        - Filmstrip (Box 76, Folder 743)
        - General Assembly Exhibit (Box 76, Folder 744)
        - Logo (Box 77, Folder 745)
        - Hymn, J.P. Huber (Box 77, Folder 746)
        - Reflections (Box 77, Folder 747)
        - Reflections -- Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 748)
        - Essays (Box 77, Folder 749)
        - Study Packet Development (Box 77, Folder 750)
        - Study Packet (2 copies) (Box 77, Folder 751)
      - Events
        - Friday Evening Program, 12 June 1987 (Box 77, Folder 752)
        - Pre-Assembly Conference on Mission, 8-9 June 1987 (Box 77, Folder 753)
        - Montreat Global Mission Conference, 19-25 July 1987 (Box 77, Folder 754)
        - Risking to Live Mission Conference, 7-10 Nov 1987 (Box 77, Folder 755)
    - Global Mission Conference, Montreat, NC
      - 1986 Conference, General (Box 78, Folder 755a)
      - 1988 Conference, General (Box 78, Folder 755b)
      - 1989 Conference: Publications (Box 78, Folder 756)
      - 1989 Conference: General Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 757)
      - 1989 Conference: International Personnel (Box 78, Folder 758)
      - 1989 Conference: Personal Profiles (Box 78, Folder 759)
      - 1989 Conference: Opocensky, Milan: Bible Leader (Box 78, Folder 760)
      - 1989 Conference: Rodriguez, Oscar: Music Leader (Box 78, Folder 761)
      - 1989 Conference: Reflection Groups (Brown, Hindman coordinators) (Box 78, Folder 762)
      - 1989 Conference: "The Same Gospel: A Changing Context," by M. Flory in Horizons Magazine, Nov.-Dec. 1988 (Box 78, Folder 762a)
      - 1989 Conference: Daily Globe (Box 78, Folder 763)
      - 1989 Conference: One-Day Program (Box 78, Folder 764)
      - 1989 Conference: Evaluations/Follow-Up (Box 78, Folder 765)
      - 1989 Conference: Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 766)
  - Other Agencies and Groups
    - United Presbyterian Women
      - Women's Relations, General
        - Fellowship Missions, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 767)
        - Ecumenical Mission Secretary Workbooks, 1958-1963 (Box 78, Folder 768)
        - International Reports, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 769)
        - General, 1960-1965 (Box 78, Folder 770)
        - Target Africa Program, 1961-1964 (Box 78, Folder 771)
        - Women's Opportunity Giving Fund, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 772)
        - Asian Encounter Study Tour: Evangelism in Japan Consultation, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 772a)
        - Program Manual, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 773)
        - Coordinating Team, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 774)
        - Third World Women, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 774a)
        - Outstanding Women in the PCUSA Exhibit, 2008 (Box 123, Folder 1316)
      - UPW National Meetings
        - General, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 775)
        - Discussion Groups, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 776)
        - Overseas Guests, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 777)
        - Publications, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 778)
        - Charter for Christian Action, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 779)
        - Panel-rama, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 780)
        - Ecumenical Guests, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 781)
        - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 782)
        - General, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 783)
        - Noonday Programs, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 784)
        - Overseas Guests, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 785)
        - General, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 786)
        - International Participants, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 787)
        - Program, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 788)
        - International Community, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 789)
        - General, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 790)
        - The Yarn (Daily Bulletin), 1982 (Box 80, Folder 791)
        - International Gathering: "Proclaim Jubilee" - Printed Material, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 791a)
    - Education
      - Board of Christian Education: Church Officer Training Program, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 792)
      - Board of Christian Education: Church Vocation Program -- Handbooks, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 793)
      - Board of Christian Education: Church Vocation Program -- General, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 794)
      - Board of Christian Education: Seminar on the Church's Mission in a Changing World, 1964-1965 (Box 80, Folder 795)
      - Board of Christian Education: Dept. of Vocation, Handbook on Counseling the Candidate (Box 80, Folder 796)
      - Division of Higher Education: Statement on the Church and Higher Education, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 797)
      - Division of Higher Education: Staff Meeting, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 798-799)
      - Task Force on the Church and Higher Education, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 799a)
      - Results of Questionnaire: "Presbyterian Panel", 1978 (Box 80, Folder 799aa)
      - Printed Educational Material, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 799ab)
    - Program Agency Miscellaneous
      - General Director's Report, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 799b)
      - Hunger Program, 1975, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 800)
      - National Presbyterian Center, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 800a)
      - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 801)
      - Board Meetings, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 802)
      - Board Planning Committee Report, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 803)
      - Board Meeting, Feb. 1980 (Box 81, Folder 804)
      - Board Meeting, Oct. 1980 (Box 81, Folder 805)
      - Education in a Global Age, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 806)
    - Support Agency
      - General, 1977-1986 (Box 81, Folder 807)
      - Interpretation and Stewardship: East Africa and South Pacific, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 808)
      - Interpretation and Stewardship Kit, 1978-1979 (Box 81, Folder 809-810)
      - Interpretation and Stewardship: Pioneers in Presbyterian Mission Portfolio (Box 81, Folder 811)
      - Global Mission Relations Materials, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 812)
    - Presbyterian Youth Triennium, 1980
      - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 813)
      - Design Team (Box 81, Folder 814)
      - Poster (Box 81, Folder 814a)
      - Evaluation Retreat (Box 82, Folder 815)
      - Information Sheets (Box 82, Folder 816)
      - International Participation (Box 82, Folder 817)
      - Program Books (Box 82, Folder 818)
      - Newsletters (Box 82, Folder 819)
      - Registration (Box 82, Folder 820)
      - Continuing the Journey: Follow-Up Materials (Box 82, Folder 821)
    - Miscellaneous
      - World Order Movement, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 822)
      - World Order Movement: Churches and a Just and Durable Peace, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 823)
      - World Presbyterian Alliance: 18th General Council, Campinas, Brazil, "The Servant Lord and His Servant People", 1959 (Box 82, Folder 823a)
      - Board of National Missions: Student Summer Service, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 824)
      - Presbytery of New York City: Committee on Ecumenical Mission and Relations, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 825)
      - Presbyterian Service and Study Projects Committee, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 826)
      - Council on Church and Society: Investment Guidelines, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 827)
      - Presbytery of New York City: General, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 828)
      - General Assembly: Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box 82, Folder 828a)
      - General Assembly: Miscellaneous, 1987-2004 (Box 82, Folder 828b)
      - General Assembly: Missions, 1975-1986 (Box 82, Folder 828c)
      - Sierra Mission Area (Sacramento, Cal.), 1978-1979 (Box 107, Folder 1220)
      - "The United Presbyterian Church in the United States of America Within the World Council of Churches", 1978 (Box 107, Folder 1221)
      - "Toward a Pluralistic Church", n.d. (Box 107, Folder 1222)
      - "Peacemaking: On Dusting the Wind" - gift to Flory, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 1223)
      - Ecumenism Among Us: A Presbyterian Conversation (Conference October 10-13, 1996, Mo-Ranch, Texas) (Box 107, Folder 1223)
      - Worldwide Ministries - Printed Material, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 1224)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 107, Folder 1225)
- Other Organizations, Series XII
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Latin American Exiles (Sergio and Marilena Schneider), 1971-1973 (Box 83, Folder 830)
  - African Affairs Seminar (Box 83, Folder 830a)
  - American Council on Education (Box 83, Folder 830b)
  - The Asia Society (Box 83, Folder 830c)
  - Asian Women's Resource Center for Culture and Theology (Box 83, Folder 830)
  - Association of Korean Christian Scholars in North America, 1977-1978 (Box 83, Folder 830e)
  - The Bridge, Washington, D.C. (Tom and Peggy Cleveland), 1970 (Box 83, Folder 831)
  - Christian Peace Conference (M. Flory, VP 1967), 1967, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 832)
  - Christians Associated for Relationships with Eastern Europe (CAREE), 1973-1987 (Box 83, Folder 833)
  - CAREE, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 834)
  - CAREE (M. Flory, membership secretary), 1989 (Box 83, Folder 835)
  - Church Women United: World Day of Prayer, 1957-1984 (Box 83, Folder 836)
  - Church Women United: General, 1963-1984 (Box 83, Folder 837)
  - Church Women United: Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 838)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Program Books, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 839)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Program/Stage Arrangements, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 340)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly, "No Longer at Ease" (Script, Hilda B. Powicke), 1967 (Box 84, Folder 841)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly, Speech, Calvin S. Hamilton, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 842)
  - Church Women United: Post-Assembly Consultation of Overseas Women, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 843)
  - Church Women United: World Order Conference, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 844)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly "Signatures of Faith", 1977 (Box 84, Folder 844a)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Program Book, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 845)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly, General, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 846)
  - Church Women United: Fortieth Anniversary, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 847)
  - Church Women United: General Director Search Committee, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 848)
  - Church Women United: U.N. Seminar on Disarmament, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 849)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Information Book, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 850)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Program Book (2 copies), 1984 (Box 84, Folder 851)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly Resource Packet, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 852)
  - Church Women United: Ecumenical Assembly, General, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 853)
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers, 1967-1971 (Box 85, Folder 854)
  - Council of Protestant Colleges and Universities: Proceedings of 6th Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 854a)
  - Council on Student Travel: General, 1961-1963 (Box 85, Folder 855)
  - Council on Student Travel: Inter-American Exchange, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 856)
  - Ecumenical Center and International Residence, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1993-1994 (Box 85, Folder 857)
  - Ecumenical Order for Mission, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 858)
  - Higher Education Ministries Arena (Box 85, Folder 858a)
  - Institute for Cultural Action (IDAC, Paulo Freire), 1971-1975 (Box 85, Folder 859)
  - Institute of Political and Social Studies (Proposed), Forman Christian College, Lahore, West Pakistan, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 859a)
  - Institute for Religion and Culture, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 860)
  - Institute of Religion and Social Change: Project Proposal, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 861)
  - INSTRAW: UN International Research and Training Institute for Advancement of Women (Box 85, Folder 861a)
  - International Documentation (IDOC) North America, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 862)
  - International Student Service, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 863)
  - Iran Bethal College, Tehran, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 864)
  - ISS: International Student Service (Box 85, Folder 864a)
  - Kirkridge Retreat Center, Bangor, Penn. (Experimental Project), 1957-1965 (Box 85, Folder 865)
  - Korean Women's Development Institute (Box 85, Folder 865a)
  - Maryville College (M. Flory, Trustee): Board of Directors, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 866)
  - Maryville College: Audit, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 867)
  - Maryville College: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 868)
  - Maryville College: Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 869)
  - Maryville College: Board of Directors, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 870)
  - Maryville College: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 871)
  - Maryville College: Board of Directors, Spring Meeting, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 872)
  - Maryville College: Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 873)
  - Maryville College: Board of Directors, Spring Meeting, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 874)
  - Maryville College: Reports and Policies, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 875)
  - Maryville College: Reports on "National student movements, overseas volunteers and international students," and student service, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 875a)
  - Midwest Center for Latino Religious Studies, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 876)
  - Mindolo Ecumenical Center, North Rhodesia, 1967-1969 (Box 86, Folder 877)
  - National Center for Public Service Internship Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 878)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1964-1983 (Box 86, Folder 879)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs: Latin American Students, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 880)
  - North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA): Correspondence, 1966-1972, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 881)
  - NACLA: Reports, 1966-1971 (Box 86, Folder 882)
  - NACLA: Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 86, Folder 883)
  - NACLA: Staff, "Mexico 1968: A Study of Domination and Repression" (Box 87, Folder 884)
  - NACLA: Black, Edie and Fred Goff, "The Hanna Industrial Complex", 1969 (Box 87, Folder 885)
  - NACLA: Klare, Michael, "The University-Military Complex: A Directory and Related Documents", 1969 (Box 87, Folder 886)